Five seconds. Users spend
only five second deciding
whether to stay on a website or leave.
And it's the UI design that determines
those five seconds.
If you want to master UI design
professionally, not just by learning
tools, rest assured you've come
to the perfect place in this course,
we'll start from the very basics.
What exactly is UI UX design?
What are visual principles?
What elements exist
in the world of user interface design?
We'll cover Gestalt, Contrast,
Layout design, Proximity
grid systems, spacing,
and a ton of other UI design fundamentals
that every successful
interface of follows.
Then we'll move on to Figma.
One of the most popular UI design
tools from its work is based on toolbar
to advance the features
that will make your workflow 100 times
faster and more consistent.
There is no fury, only content
in this course.
Every chapter includes a hands
on exercises and a real world project.
Together we'll write a design for it.
Create mood boards
and wireframes, design user flows,
and more from wireframes
interactive prototypes.
The highlight of this course
starts from chapter six,
where we'll work on a real
UI design project called the Real Life
Financial App,
along with its landing website.
Exactly as it happens
in the real professional world.
After.
In this project,
we'll dive into design
thinking principles and UI structuring,
a professional design system
and a style guide.
Complete a fully developed via frame.
And most importantly,
learn how to design responsive
layouts for tablets and mobile devices.
We'll also deeply explore graphic design
topics such as color and typography.
Applying the 6030 ten rule, color harmony,
understanding color systems and wheels,
color accessibility, and creating small,
functional color palettes
that serve
as the foundation of every great project.
The interactive phase is there.
You bring a project to life
with advanced prototypes, text
animations, sections, schools, carousels,
and practical interactions.
You'll be able to design
something very close to a real website.
And for those who want to collaborate
in the team, we'll cover
dev mode libraries, file publishing,
and community, and many other tabs
to make sure your files are fully ready
for handoff
to developers.
In this course, we don't stop
at the free version of Figma.
We've also prepared a separate chapter
using the professional subscription
of this powerful tool
to teach you advanced the features
and deeper layers of the UI design.
And finally, what's the outcome for you?
A professional portfolio
with real projects in demand, skills
for the job market,
and a complete design workflow
that takes you from idea to final product.
I'm Alex as Leonie,
your instructor in this course,
and I'll be guiding you
every step of the way in as login website.
See you in the course.